Itai Mizlish

0542258899

itaim148@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/itai-mizlish/

https://github.com/itaim18

Portfolio: https://itaimiz.com

I am a highly motivated Front-end Developer and web developer with a strong understanding of React.js, its methods and hooks. Experienced in building front-end and full-stack architectures from scratch. Proficient in UI/UX through CSS tools (Sass, Tailwind, Bootstrap). Learned DS implementation and algorithms solving in JavaScript and ES6. A Computer Science graduate in highschool and a self learner.

Professional Experience

Front End Developer | 2022 - Present

- Designed and created architectures for web applications.
- Developed fullstack web apps using MERN structure and firebase.
- Using Javascript libraries in CSS and SASS to create user interfaces.
- Experienced in functional programming in Javascript and knowledgeable in ES6.

Tutor | 2016 - 2018

Israeli Center for Advancement in Math (associated with Bar Ilan University)

- Facilitated annual Science Day activities for children.
- Tutored basic Physics and Aeronautics lessons in schools in the TA Metropolitan Area.
- Graded tests and tutored children with special needs.

Education

JCT Lev Academic Center
Bachelor in Science in Computer Science | 2015 - 2019

Certificates

The complete 2022 Web development Bootcamp | Udemy React - The Complete Guide | Udemy JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass | Udemy

Military Service

Infantry Unit | 2019 - 2022

Volunteering

Krembo Wings | 2015 - 2018

Assisted and accompanied children with special needs and formed unique connections with them.

Languages

Hebrew - Mother tongue | English - Excellent